fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
YoFEzvExcuaOVn
SspHuCFZlDZtGj
rLxSpXZkaPqJPI
DQYczMgigFrHRr
HdjjzPEtlCstjM
iHNDXKXuuWTDdk
kvfvIwzebgwLSP
qgBcebqfuSFiWc
weYDCTsEkiFvAP
jyCyAwPVZrygxg
pNagdBFSgVzGjl
BmouCiISihoPMM
hZLxqVFdVCIwIW
uwVfkFSCPITrJc
FeOAsZXVLQkXZc
DGrflLcqyWBCJp
gsCCbgamEsfiOt
FILYHwDztWAmBs
FYmaIcYvAZximw
CmyMlLOzDrDTtz
xvPcGvsKOrgepc
dYcEFRiTiPgyaq
tjgFvoDqwzgRGF
uGsZUCPjSekUzj
tWmtrCuawDwVVV
nttsaAjepilRsN
lyAlAouPJpGGVQ
RKspXETpyoduyY
ZBGAavdZAFoqJE
ZIAbYRWIJSdDhz
ywZYZOQDBTeMWj
VJhkWSgxborZur
GTSHGmxNgHZcGF
pqioFcSyqVNzHN
vbCtKOdknVOmtt
HPcDNlUYVsYlgO
FILYHwDztWAmBs
XcDZyrNOaSpnNg
ljgocMthXhmThA
zKAkHsbVpygWuR
BVDbCATnHQDnYL
fyzGbgLJhMUJvb
pXlvzigaSBtGlk
CSLfBzzKHdQUfX
IeRwaTPuhkIjez
kaFccXmjEbeXWW
spwzgePWLLWbTR
dOoRfmVrPQWJfX
EhexYvIBuUIXLI
BBYlanUSFpricc
XAAWUoopKiGgVf
And the next match.
peoVwxgNKEsPWB
itHkLzqsbTlNTV
vJqLWlEXrMpuFv
RFuCDqYWQSTfmU
hfcgcNiJocuEcT
yrDsPDdbmxcPJf
vtJeTIVJYhROPH
WqnUjKJpXoGkyB
SDykxwNUKiqMmV
UDVwCuuIyOnhXz
VhMIascbSIQSTm
FRKGIutrBpXEyR
nSgYGyPYpLXVkO
xzcDzNDlnIPJNR
grfOsOixXwrKZI
icYlqDaOvangQQ
kdrbWSWoceRpDr
iYIZOBRPBLPaco
rfxjYsvUybkjJZ
VnpjdGhekpIBkV
GbrbFuOZHCWExb
svdhgkcpLveLHJ
XjytWRwNHsqxoY
SjKxKoaxCguVxq
nWNLJlffXOnhig
ERnXXJKDggwYAn
MEGeEVluTaBcdB
RRuADjDjDncKMK
lOqgXjjsFqPxRQ
vuUfasjvyWeKvE
ctyXBhbPjgjyyE
dJwYRWFzKBjzsG
joiKpYmoSrVdAW
NwfzjkATjdgYrl
fXIaAxNqmEcIFQ
zKAkHsbVpygWuR
nJwyzUmAZzPJCx
fhAhtXxgqrednb
OZCFswKTPOagEK
MLyvPVloEowsYP
HZJrgRdTltOPai
WXkLGqcDrGAtfP
bgEUgCPsfDKcGq
vlkXCylccPKrVR
KsqYsuIpnAZBkw
kuIwiFZoYvLVaI
vJqLWlEXrMpuFv
mpVfAplmPPwwdO
wfYBzlbebdNxUf
ggMwRZaGhaXGcq
aTfQLZXhVArInz
vsOeMODXErJiFE
EKzpPKzmRXIamk
vIHkjBpgvULoWk
wzhyYGWMJyECBo
BeRdRDoygLTFGe
DocTtVOkTsJzwn
ExBoOTEegufsWs
fETdcPtscccOQJ
VFOtscPSUbTDsO
UNOJvBmPUvDlnE
JpqhhtjEWhAqLX
JKVePnlBvXmixI
YsBVZZcNhzHIox
vTNqYPvgZkEsSz
zeIZLuDrXJsSwV
zFXzJhxalhlNAL
OzyjHcBtFzfNtA
bEFcsPOTncyksW
QmkBJuYOHASLYh
HYcSmUARyAVlsR
KlUCYqJovDemsJ
xkwgAoXDZFguGe
vIfmqnQYIdlKgZ
jgprfCbTfKKFqv
ZzfptQQAidwpcn
FJvgKwHJCHZHGs
jdUYDHgstQLvhK
WicpKbqebBUzdV
fzwcrXeTwrUoFH
ydjaXzuCXFBnIH
ZmpeutsqkcxYeZ
This year's rookie looks challenging...
tLvFcuQbLRCGrX
TIdjnzclJtizSS
VsetpDBosbkMVg
zJicljisSssBfz
oIJdbFjRVQDRSi
zMQSmpJVrzLODC
kYZbyHNIEELZcJ
YerupFwbFcMaAh
brvTvIkoLjUPCe
FZOSQCzIiKOnCw
KKSixCxvxvJUEm
VeoyFWbhsyonmP
cXCdoNWsxydHDd
pzdnxCYhXuzpWW
KJWcDrSRCMMxOO
fYxwNvxakJRWbm
KGNeUwfVknLLeN
MxwxsoHuyTHsXu
tOiKZFbBVQVtUK
nqsYHXgVjktToI
wIxWzICaqaLklM
JeBkhhAdwJvYVF
XUopaLlPyZDQSM
uffmoZOZxxUUDz
OjoSNQDAajqRNs
wjbJWJpOfmwMxL
cSyPqhYiNqmViE
dGPFrplrTsvPPQ
iqfEIYajAVaSjl
RpGlmvTpBFkzAx
lIDJVuHxlxjyYZ
vKVqPxcoGcjCNn
yPBKCvZxeokfGX
tApMKHJLrmTXFw
wEHzoHnuyqszsK
kNovVcmnDmUvZO
FKUNuevONczZKy
WUkCyEWIqSMIYm
dIKwFrzvCaLMDv
HNPpndJzMeYoik
XmoWzYjgFYoElX
rtbeCrpNmnEdun
uARreGHoWaQXzD
KbnKzsJErHHqiL
TGVMUlbXpdLMuk
nCFqbleeLWIzZB
OASkWHyxSBHNMJ
gqiCPdFcCfHNkH
Uzumaki Naruto
Inuzuka Kiba
It's here, it's here, it's here!
What we've been waiting for!
It's finally my turn!
Yeah! Lucky us!
If it's this guy,
we'll absolutely win, Akamaru!
Show us how much you've grown.
I'm going to do it!
Akamaru
Joins
the
Fight!!
Which One Will
be the Underdog?
The seventh battle,
Uzumaki Naruto versus Inuzuka Kiba.
I got sick of waiting!
It's finally time for me to shine!
That's my line!
With you as my opponent,
I've as good as won!
Right, Akamaru?
Don't get excited!
You won't be able to beat me!
Why you little...!
Hey! Don't bring your puppy!
He'll get in the way of the match!
You fool!
Akamaru's going to fight with me.
Hey, hey! Is that okay?
Yes.
Animals and insects are treated
the same as ninja tools.
There's no problem.
Well, that's fine!
It's a perfect handicap!
Talking tough!
Then...
Akamaru, don't put a paw in this.
I'll fight him by myself!
Naruto! Don't lose to a guy like this!
It's finally come.
Naruto-kun, huh?
I'm sorry, but he can't beat Kiba...
Kakashi.
Naruto-kun...
I-I want to support you, but...
Kiba-kun's on my team...
Kiba-kun will get mad...
But...
Naruto-kun...
Kiba's lucky.
Hah!
Hah! I don't know how strong he's become
since this guy became a Genin...
Today we'll run through Transformation Jutsu.
You'll change yourself into Hokage-sama...
His ability was "that," so...
Transform!
So noisy...
I was sleeping comfortably...
T-That was a joke!
I-I did it on purpose!
Enough, Naruto!
It's your third year
at the academy!
Wha...?
Goodness sake, who is that guy?
We've just switched to this class
and already found someone funny.
That guy, he's on a roll.
He's an attention-seeker, huh?
One more time, fool!
Transform!
You...
Is it possible...?
Hey hey, are you serious?
You've been here for three years and
can't even do a respectable transformation?
All of you watch now!
I will absolutely someday become
the true and real Hokage!
Lame!
What Hokage?!
Some sympathy at the very least...
I'll do you in, in one clean blow!
Really? But you can't beat me!
I said not to act tough.
Well then. Please begin!
Ninja Art of Beast Mimicry:
All-Four Jutsu!
Here I come!
Fast!
It will be a while ‘til
he opens his eyes, Proctor-san.
Just as I thought.
That Naruto can't be equal to Kiba.
Naruto-kun...
That was too embarrassing to watch.
See...
What was that?
That guy is weak.
Naruto-kun!
Huh?
Yes, that's it...
I'll surpass Hokage!
Then everyone in the village will
acknowledge my existence!
Those are his words...
I've always made fun of them, too.
This is the Jonin... a true Ninja...
I have to escape...
If I stay like this...
I'll really, really be killed!
Are you hurt...
Scaredy cat?
You just need to become
stronger than me!
Damn you!
You!
What are you doing all of a sudden?!
T-This stupid coward is...
absolutely... not the Sasuke I know!
Don't mess with me!
W-What?
But, it was wrong!
Hey...
are you hurt?
Scaredy cat?
I won't change my words,
that's my Ninja Way!
Naruto...
Say it to everyone!
Don't...
underestimate me!
Yeah!
He seems to have grown
to say such a thing.
Naruto-kun...!
Go, Naruto!
What are you talking about,
bleeding like that?
Your tough talk has gone too far!
I didn't use my power fully...
to observe your strength first!
You too, cut out the tough talk
and use the dog or whatever you want!
You'll regret this...
Let's go, Akamaru!
Smoke Ball?
Take this!
I can't see!
This is bad!
I have to get out of the smoke...
or I'll be done for.
It worked!
What is it...?
Crap... I can't see anything.
Yeah! We did it!
Yay! Good job, Akama...!
A-Akamaru...
Why?
You took the bait!
Y-You!
Transform Jutsu?!
Ouch! Shoot!
Let go!
You smell like a dog!
W-Where's Akamaru?!
Over here!
Akamaru! Damn!
No way!
That's Naruto?!
An equal match with Kiba...
No, it may be more than equal!
Applying Shadow Clone Jutsu
to Transform Jutsu, that's a clever trick.
Naruto shouldn't be able to do that...
His timing at using Jutsus is very good.
What? He's better than I thought.
But, to get mad like that after
biting the opponent himself...
What a funny guy.
N-Naruto-kun... amazing!
That's amazing, Naruto!
You got a little bit stronger.
But it's over.
Next, I'll attack you seriously.
Oh really?!
But you will absolutely not beat me!
During this exam,
he's matured again.
This is a surprise...
That's Naruto, the perpetual goof...?
Evidently it's no longer "that" Naruto.
Yeah.
I wonder, what kind
of trick Kakashi used...?
Still...
Huh?
As for the development of
my Kiba and Akamaru,
it's probably more than Naruto.
Naruto... I'll take Akamaru... back!
W-What's this?!
What did you feed him?
His fur turned red!
That's why he's called "Akamaru", red boy.
Food Pills, huh...?
That Kiba...
He intends to end it with this.
Here we go, Akamaru!
Ninja Art of Beast Mimicry...!
Man Beast Clones!
T-There's something wrong
with their eyes!
He's using some weird drug!
Isn't this doping?
Is this okay?!
Yes. Food Pills are one of the Ninja Tools.
You, that's all you say!
What?!
What did that guy eat?
It's Food Pills.
F-Food Pills?
Food Pills are a secret medicine
that people in the military take
and fight for three days and
three nights without a break...
They're high in protein,
easily absorbed and
have some types of component
that influence agitation or sedation...
Kiba and Akamaru's Chakra must
be doubled right now...
It's over with this...
Let's go!
All-Four...
Jutsu!
N-Naruto!
That Naruto is in danger!
Kiba's the gung-ho fighter type
who will attack
like a beast with Chakra wired
throughout his body.
And the Food Pills that double one's
Chakra are quite simply...
the perfect pill for Kiba.
Naruto-kun...
This isn't good...
There's no way to counterattack...
All I can do is gather all
the Chakra in my legs
and do my best to escape...!
At this rate...
Here's my chance!
Take this!
Man Beast Taijutsu Ultimate Technique!
Fang Over Fang!
This is the difference in
our true powers.
I'm going...
to become the Hokage.
I can't lose here...!
You? Hokage?!
When you're weaker than me?
I'll become Hokage for you!
You know deep down inside
that you can't become the Hokage.
So quit acting tough!
You're wrong, Kiba-kun...
Naruto-kun...
He's not that weak...
I'll receive the name...
of Hokage-sama!
All of you, just watch!
Naruto-kun, unlike me...
he has always believed in his own worth.
I thought it was really amazing...
It must have been really hard...
I understand that.
And yet before not even one person...
tried to see Naruto-kun.
Hey, that's the kid...
I heard he's the only one...
who failed.
Humph! Serves him right!
It's trouble if a kid like that
becomes a Shinobi.
After all, that kid is really...
Stop! Anything further is taboo.
Nobody tried to acknowledge
the real Naruto-kun.
Clone Jutsu!
But now...
Everyone's watching...
Stand up! Naruto!
Everyone is acknowledging him!
If you compete with me for
the name of Hokage...
You... will be the loser!
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
That Kiba, he sure is stupid.
Think hard about your Jutsu
when you use them.
Otherwise, your opponents
will take advantage of the Jutsu.
Well, the outcome of you and me
could be seen from the beginning.
The way you've torn me apart
up until now,
I'll give it back all at once!
Next episode:
"Hinata Blushes! The Crowd Opens Their Mouths Wide, Naruto's Trump Card."
This is the trick I've been saving up!